

DURGA PRASAD

I am a 4th Year Undergrad at NSUT(East Campus) Delhi pursuing B.Tech in ECE. I have basic knowledge at Data Structures and algorithms and have a strong foundation in cpp and Logical Problem Solving. Experienced in working on the latest Web development technologies ranging from React Js, Node Js, and Boostrap, and basics like HTML, CSS, and Javascript.

North East Delhi, Delhi, India

github.com/jztlucky6264

8178872928

in linkedin.com/in/durga-prasad-yadav-19b6851b7

medium.com/@luckyyadav6264

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology(ECE) NSUT East Campus (AIACT&R)

2019 - Present 8.0 CGPA

Higher Secondary(12)

GOVT. Boys Senior Secondary School(Yamuna Vihar Delhi-53)

2018 82 Percentage

Secondary School(10)

GOVT. Boys Senior Secondary School(Yamuna Vihar Delhi-53)

2016 7.9 CGPA

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Chrome Extension

- I have created chrome extension which gives code of selected color
- Stack used TypeScript, CSS3, Github, Chrome Extension Store
- Github Repository Link

Resume Finder

- This is a website where we provide resume of students who have placed in different companies recently
- Stack used React Js, CSS3, Bootstrap, Semantic UI,Scss,BrowserRouter,Framer motion
- Project Link
- Github Repository link

Search Engine Of Github

- It is website for finding the github user
- Stack used React Js, CSS3, Bootstrap
- Project Link
- Github Repository Link

Portfolio

- It is a simple and responsive portfolio website I designed it using only React Js, Material UI, and Framer-motion.
- The portfolio shows details of a few of my other projects.
- Project Link
- Github Repository Link

SKILLS

Html Css Javascript React Js Boostrap

CPP Data Structures and Algorithms

WORK EXPERIENCE

The Sparks Foundation (WEB DEVELOPER INTERN) (03/2022 - 04/2022)

In this internship, I have made a project on Basic Banking system using HTML, CSS, REACT JS, BOOTSTRAP, FIREBASE - Github repository

VR AR MR Technology (WEB DEVELOPER INTERN) (09/2022 - Present)

In this internship in first week I Worked on Project of company portfolio website, I write frontend code and 80% of backend code using - HTML,CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP, PHP.

Certificate Name

Complete JAVASCRIPT with HTML5,CSS3 from zero to Expert-2022 -- from coursera

INTERESTS

Web Development Aws App Development

Web Real-Time Communications